Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5900
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
1933-1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5900
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Files from Southern Pacific Transportation Company and Washington Gas Light Company are included in this collection.
5731967
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Dr. Jacob Seidenberg (1914-1996) was a government official who specialized in labor arbitration and non-discrimination contracts, and wrote extensively on labor law and negotiations. He graduated from Temple University in 1937 and received a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania Law School in 1941. During the 1940s he was an attorney with the U.S. War Department, the National War Labor Board and the National Wage Stabilization Board. In 1948 he went to graduate school at Cornell University, from which he earned his Ph.D. in industrial and labor relations in 1951. In 1951 he joined the staff of the President's Committee on Government Contract Compliance. The Committee was abolished by President Dwight D. Eisenhower in August 1953 by Executive Order 10479 and was succeeded by the President's Committee on Government Contracts. Seidenberg was appointed Executive Director of the new committee and served until January 1960 when he resigned to become a full-time labor arbitrator. The Committee was responsible for enforcing non-discrimination clauses in government contracts, worked with private businesses to help them overcome job discrimination, and developed educational programs against ethnic and racial discrimination. The chairman was Vice President Richard Nixon, and the vice chairman was Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell. In later years Seidenberg served on a number of boards of inquiry involving labor disputes. From 1970 to 1975 he was chairman of the Federal Services Impasses Panel which settled deadlocks in federal labor negotiations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5031 A&B: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5032: Jacob Seidenberg Injunction Study 5175: Jacob Seidenberg Taft-Hartley Maritime Dispute Records 5194: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Files 5217: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Case Files 5229: Jacob Seidenberg Additional records 5468: Jacob Seidenberg Arbitration files 5519: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5571: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5605: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5635: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5666: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5706: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5756: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5773: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5808: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5935: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5953: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5988: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
Seidenberg, Jacob; Southern Pacific Transportation Company.; Washington Gas Light Company.
5731967
- Southern Pacific Railroad (Box 1)
  - Special Board of Adjustment-1002: Awards, Vol. 1, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Special Board of Adjustment no. 1002: Awards Vol. 2, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Special Board of Adjustment no. 1002: Awards Vol. 3, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - E and F O-6-12 1002-27, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - E and F O-7-66 1002-28, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - E and F O-5-37 1002-29, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - E and F W-5-41 1002-30, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - E and F T-4-60 1002-31, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - E and F W-5-54 1002-32, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - E and F O-5-84 1002-33, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - E and F T-6-46 1002-34, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - E and F T-6-47 1002-35, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - E and F O-5-47 1002-36, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - E and F O-5-48 1002-37, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - E and F 7-O-114 1002-38, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - E and F O-6-10 1002-39, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - E and F T-5-91 1002-40, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - E and F O-6-20 1002-41, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - E and F O-6-34 1002-42, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - E and F O-6-42 1002-43, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - E and F W-6-45 1002-44, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - E and F 7-L-113 1002-45, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - E and F J-6-53 1002-46, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - E and F L-6-29 1002-47, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - E and F L-7-99 1002-48, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - E and F O-6-102 1002-49, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - E and F 7-W-123 1002-50, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Southern Pacific Railroad (Box 2)
  - E and F O-6-23 1002-69, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - E and F 9-W-3 1002-70, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - E and F 8-L-36 1002-71, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - E and F O-5-60 1002-72, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - E and F O-5-59 1002-73, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - E and F 1-TUC-O-3 1002-74, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - E and F A-JAC-2-62 1002-75, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - E and F 8-5-22 1002-76, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - E and F 9-O-5 1002-77, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - E and F 9-O-4 1002-78, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - E and F 7-S-116 1002-79, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - E and F A-SAC-1-67 1002-86, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - E and F O-7-49 1002-87, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - E and F B-TUC-D-9 1002-88, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - E and F O-SHA-8 1002-89, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - E and F O-TUC-6 1002-90, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - E and F O-LOS-17 1002-91, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - E and F 1-ORE-1 1002-92, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - E and F O-TUC-27 1002-93, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - E and F O-THC-21 1002-94, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - E and F O-LOS-29 1002-95, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - E and F 1-LOS-2 1002-96, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Washington Gas Light Co and United Parcel Service (Box 3)
  - Washington Gas Light Company Transcript Pages 1-260, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    March 31, 1989
  - Washington Gas Light Company Transcript Pages 25-195, 233-240, 247-261, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    January 29, 1990
  - Washington Gas Light Company In Camera Session Transcript Pages 196-232, 246, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Washington Gas Light Company Transcript Pages 1-296, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    June 19, 1990
  - Washington Gas Light Company Transcript Pages 587-840, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    January 22, 1990
  - Washington Gas Light Company Transcript Pages 297-586, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    June 30, 1990
  - Washington Gas Light Company Transcript Pages 1-240, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    October 10, 1990
  - United Parcel Service Letter of Understanding, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    February 27, 1990
  - United Parcel Service Grievance Case No. 90-31, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    March 14, 1990
  - United Parcel Service Correspondence and Service Analysis, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - United Parcel Service Completed Survey Forms (Folder 1 of 7), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - United Parcel Service Completed Survey Forms (Folder 2 of 7), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - United Parcel Service Completed Survey Forms (Folder 3 of 7), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - United Parcel Service Case CM 90-31-4/90-B7 Transcript, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    April 24, 1990
  - United Parcel Service Case No. 90-31 Transcript, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    September 24, 1990
  - United Parcel Service Case No. 90-31 Exhibit 1 Agreement, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Exxon, Health Care Finance Administration, and Railroads (Box 4)
  - Exxon Company Transcript, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    August 24, 1988
  - Health Care Finance Administration FMCS Case No. 88-00654, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    March 7, 1988
  - Health Care Finance Administration Case No. 88-00654, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    May 22, 1988
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Conditions Carriers' Pre-Hearing Brief, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    May 17, 1988
  - Norfolk Southern Corporation New York Dock Protective Conditions Employees' Submission, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 1 Working Copy, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 1 Clean Copy, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    August 7, 1990
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 1 Working Copy, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 2 Clean Copy, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 3 Working Copy, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 3 Clean Copy, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 4 and No. 5 Working Copy, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 4 and No.5 Clean Copy, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 6 Working Copy, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Public Law Board No. 4895 Docket No. 6 Clean Copy, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Southern Pacific Public Law Board No. 4993, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Case 230-NYD-0064 B Correspondence, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Case 230-NYD-0064 B Exhibits, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Case A-11547 Exhibit, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    April 7, 1987
- AMTRAK and the District of Columbia (Box 5)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4762 Employees Ex-Parte Submission, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4762 Employes Ex-Parte Exhibits, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4762 Employes Ex-Parte Exhibits 21-45, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4762 Employes Ex-Parte Exhibits 46-60, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4762 Amtrak's Ex-Parte Exhibits 1-7, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4762 Amtrak's Ex-Parte Exhibit 8, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4762 Amtrak's Ex-Parte Exhibits 9-40, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4970 Amtrak's Ex-Parte Submissions, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4970 Amtrak's Ex-Parte Exhibits 1-13, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4970 Amtrak's Ex-Parte Division 1-4, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4970 Amtrak's Ex-Parte PLB Awards and Rebuttal Exhibits 1-6, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4970 Employes Submission Vol. 1, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4970 Employes Submission Vol. 2, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Amtrak-Public Law Board No. 4970 Employes Post-Hearing Submission, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - District of Columbia-Case No. 16 39 00133 88S Correspondence, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia-Case No. 16 39 00133 88S Transcript, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - District of Columbia-Case No. 16 39 00133 88S Exhibits, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Sourcebook of Union Government Structure and Procedures, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Railroads and US Patent Office (Box 6)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Expedited Public Law Board No. 4595 Case No. 1, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Expedited Public Law Board No. 4595 Case No. 2, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Expedited Public Law Board No. 4595 Case No. 4, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Expedited Public Law Board No. 4595 Case No. 5, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Expedited Public Law Board No. 4595 Case No. 6, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Expedited Public Law Board No. 4595 Case No. 7, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Public Law Board No. 3742 Case No. 1, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Public Law Board No. 3742 Case No. 2, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Public Law Board No. 3742 Case No. 3, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Public Law Board No. 3742 Case No. 4, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Public Law Board No. 3742 Case No. 5, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Public Law Board No. 3742 Case No. 6, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Public Law Board No. 3742 Case No. 7, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - US Patent and Trademark Office Hearing on Ground Rules Dispute, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    September 12, 1983
  - US Patent and Trademark Office Hearing on Ground Rules Dispute (copy 2), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - US Patent and Trademark Office Case No. 83 FSIP 39 Transcript, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    October 11, 1983
  - US Patent and Trademark Office Case No. 83 FSIP 39 Transcript, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    November 17, 1983
  - US Patent and Trademark Office Case No. 83 FSIP 39 Transcript, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    January 11, 1984
  - US Patent and Trademark Office Case No. 83 FSIP 39 Transcript, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    January 12, 1984
  - Southern Pacific Railroad Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 Awards No. 16-23, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Southern Pacific Railroad Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 Awards 23-80, 84-85, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Southern Pacific Railroad (Box 7)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F-A-TUC-1-45 Decision No. 9, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F O-4-46 Decision No. 16, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F A-LA-O Decision No. 17, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F A-LA-O-55 Decision No. 18, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F A-TUC-O-32 Decision No. 19, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 011-181 (P) -1 Decision No. 20, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 011-181 (P) - 2 Decision No. 21, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 011-181 (B) and 011-181 (K) Decision No. 22, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F A-LA-O-14 Decision No.23, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8-O-20 Decision No. 51, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8-W-16 Decision No. 52, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8-L-39 Decision No. 53, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8_L-23 Decision No. 54, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F W-6-28 Decision No. 55, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F T-7-78 Decision No. 56, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 7-L124 Decision No. 57 (folder 1 of 2), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 7-L124 Decision No. 57 (folder 2 of 2), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8-O-10 Decision No. 58, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8-O-29 Decision No. 59, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8-L-26 Decision No. 60, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F T-6-33 Decision No. 61, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F T-6-34 Decision No. 62, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F A-ORE-1-6 Decision No. 63, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8-O-11 Decision No. 64, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 7-P-125 Decision No. 65, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 7-5-117 Decision No. 66, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8-O-33 Decision No. 67, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 8-O-38 Decision No. 68, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 9-L-7 Decision No. 84, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. TRN 8-L-39 Decision No. 85, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- American Bank Stationery Co., USAir, and Railroads (Box 8)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 1, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 2, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 3, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 4, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 5 and 6, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 8, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 11, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 12, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 14, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 15, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Public Law Board No. 4948 Case No. 16, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Burlington Northern Railroad Public Law Board No. 5007 Case No. 1 Carriers Submission, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Burlington Northern Railroad Public Law Board No. 5007 Case No. 1 Employees Submission, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Burlington Northern Railroad Public Law Board No. 5007 Case No. 2 Carrier's Submission, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Burlington Northern Railroad Public Law Board No. 5007 Case No. 2 Employees Submission, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Southern Railway Public Law Board No. 4807 Case No. 1, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - USAir Pilots' System Board of Adjustment Colbath Grievance No. 87-1-1, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - American Bank Stationery Company FMCS Case No. 88-23323, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Board of Education of St. Mary's County Case No. 16 39 00157 87S, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Trump's Castle Hotel Casino Case No. 14 300 1132 87 M, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Amtrak BRAC-US-2419, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Rockingham Poultry Marketing FMCS Case No. 86-26192, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Union Pacific Railroad New York Dock Conditions, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - American Federation of Teachers Case No. 16 30 00181 87S, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Washington Gas Light Company OPEIU, Local No. 2, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- AMTRAK and Railroads (Box 9)
  - Amtrak Public Law Board No. 4762 No Smoking Policy, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Amtrak Public Law Board No. 4762 No Smoking Policy Awards to Amtrak's Exparte Submission, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Amtrak Public Law Board No. 4762 No Smoking Policy Amtrak Exhibits No. 1-7, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Amtrak Public Law Board No. 4762 No Smoking Policy Amtrak Exhibit No 8, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Amtrak Public Law Board No. 4762 Amtrak Exhibits No. 9-29, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Amtrak Public Law Board No. 4762 No Smoking Policy Amtrak Exhibits No. 30-49, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Amtrak Public Law Board No. 4762 No Smoking Policy Employees Exhibits No. 61-64, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Amtrak Public Law Board No. 4762 No Smoking Policy Carrier Federal Laws, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Carrier's Prehearing Submissions, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    May 25, 1989
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Carrier's Exhibit Vol. 1 No. 1-31 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Carrier's Exhibit Vol. 2 No. 32-48, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Employees Submission, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Employee's Exhibits No. 2 and 3, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    June 8, 1989
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Carrier's Exhibit No. 49, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    June 9, 1989
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Joint Exhibit No. 2, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Carrier's Additional Exhibit, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    June 16, 1989
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Employees Post-Hearing Submission, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    June 23, 1989
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Carrier's Post-Hearing Submission, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Carrier's Post-Hearing Exhibits No. 49-54, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Employees' Rebuttal, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    June 30, 1989
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Carrier's Rebuttal, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Arbitration Findings, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    July 26, 1989
  - Norfolk and Western Railway New York Dock Protective Conditions Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Southern Pacific Railroad Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 Awards No. 58-72, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Southern Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 7-L-124 Decision No. 57 Exhibits 8 and 8A, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Southern Pacific Railroad and American Air Lines (Box 10)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 9-O-10 Decision No. 81, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 9-O-13 Decision No. 82, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 9-O-13 Decision No. 82 Exhibits A-I, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 9-O-13 Decision No. 82 Exhibits J1-J4 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 9-O-13 Decision No. 82 Exhibits K-M, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 1002 File No. E and F 9-3-11 Decision No. 83, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - American Airlines Grievance No. P-03-88 Vol. 1, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    January 19, 1989
  - American Airlines Grievance No. P-03-88 Vol. 2, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    January 20, 1989
  - American Airlines Grievance No. P-03-88 Employees Post-Hearing Brief, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    April 24, 1989
  - American Airlines Grievance No. P-03-88 Airlines' Closing Argument, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - American Airlines Grievance No. P-03-88 Employees Reply to Post-Hearing Brief, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    May 1, 1989